Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- S
  - Sitock, George, 1950s; cuid2128 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sivetz, Michael, undated; cuid2129 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sjuren, Harold, 2000; cuid2130 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Skrzypczak, Casmir, undated; cuid2131 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Skurla, George M., circa 1982; cuid2132 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Slack, 1954; cuid2133 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Slaughter, John B., undated; cuid2134 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Slutsky, Simon, 1978; cuid2135 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Slyke, Richard Van, undated; cuid2136 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Smith, E. B. L., undated; cuid2137 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Edward J., 1964; cuid2138 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Gregory D., undated; cuid2139 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Harrison, undated; cuid2140 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Smith, James M., 2000; cuid2141 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Joseph S., undated; cuid2142 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Kate, undated; cuid2143 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Stanley, undated; cuid2144 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Snitroff, Joseph, undated; cuid2145 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Snyder, Joel, 1996; cuid2146 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Soehngen, Henry F., undated; cuid2147 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Soffer, Jonathan, undated; cuid2148 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sokolsky, Saul, undated; cuid2149 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Solimene, Nicholas, undated; cuid2150 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Richard, undated; cuid2151 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Soros, Paul, undated; cuid2152 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Soutar, Charles F., circa 1997; cuid2153 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Soviero, Joseph C., circa 1996; cuid2154 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Sparacino, Robert R., undated; cuid2155 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Spellane, Peter, undated; cuid2156 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Spenadel, Paul, undated; cuid2157 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Spencer, William J., 1987; cuid2158 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sprinsky, William Lt. Col., undated; cuid2159 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Spruclt, Albert E., undated; cuid2160 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Squire, Edward J., 1956; cuid2161 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Stancu, Alina, undated; cuid2162 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - St. Lawrence, Jim, undated; cuid2163 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Steck, Paul G., undated; cuid2164 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Steele, Stuart, undated; cuid2165 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Stefanis, Anthony, undated; cuid2166 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Steigman, Joseph, undated; cuid2167 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Steil, Leonard, undated; cuid2168 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Stein, Richard S., undated; cuid2169 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Stein, Sidney J., undated; cuid2170 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Steinberg, Gerald M., 1956; cuid2171 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Steingut, Stanley, undated; cuid2172 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Steneck, Eugene, undated; cuid2173 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Sterling Drug, undated; cuid2174 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Sterling, Frank, undated; cuid2175 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Sterling, John, undated; cuid2176 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Stern, Henry Root, undated; cuid2177 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Sternberg, Sy, circa 2006; cuid2178 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Stevens, Joseph, undated; cuid2179 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Stever, H. Guyford, 1975; cuid2180 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Stidham, James A., 1956; cuid2181 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Stiel, Leonard, undated; cuid2182 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Stoll, Eric D., undated; cuid2183 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stolze, William, 1959, 1981; cuid2184 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Stouraitis, Thanos, undated; cuid2185 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Strang, Charles D., 1985; cuid2186 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Strauss, Fred J., undated; cuid2187 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Strauss, Simon D., 1977, 1986; cuid2188 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Streubel, Ernest John, circa 1948; cuid2189 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Strom, Gordon, undated; cuid2190 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Strybing, Herman Frederick, 1880s (reproductions); cuid2191 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Suarez, Humbert, undated; cuid2192 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Sudarsky, Jerry M., 1964, 1971, 1974; cuid2193 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Suel, Torsten, undated; cuid2194 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Sull, Won Bong, undated; cuid2195 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Sulzer, Henri G., undated; cuid2196 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Sun, Yun-Suan, undated; cuid2197 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Sung, Peter, circa 1987; cuid2198 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Suttles, Sandy, undated; cuid2199 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Sviedrys, Romualdes, 1975; cuid2200 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Swackhamer, Farris S., undated; cuid2201 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Swan, David, undated; cuid2202 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Swanson, Jeanne, undated; cuid2203 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Swartz, Jerome, undated; cuid2204 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Sweeney, Richard, 1986; cuid2205 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Sylvester, William R., circa 1980; cuid2206 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Szeglin, Arthur, undated; cuid2207 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- T
  - Tai, Meihua, undated; cuid2208 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Talberth, Henry, undated; cuid2209 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Talley, Charles P., 1982; cuid2210 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Tam, Wai Nam, undated; cuid2211 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Tamir, Theodor, undated; cuid2212 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Teng, Hualiang (Harry), undated; cuid2213 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Teraoka, Iwao, undated; cuid2214 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Terzouli, Andrew J., undated; cuid2215 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Tesoro, Giuliana, circa 1986; cuid2216 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Tevonian, Ronald, circa 1998; cuid2217 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Thevanayagam, Theva, undated; cuid2218 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Thomas, Daniel J., 1950s; cuid2219 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Thompson, Carol, undated; cuid2220 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Thompson, Harley, undated; cuid2221 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Thompson, Michael, 2009; cuid2222 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Thorne, undated; cuid2223 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Thorsen, Richard, 1980, 1986, 1998; cuid2224 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Throndsen, Elton C., 1955; cuid2225 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Thurber, Elmer, undated; cuid2226 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Tobias, Abraham Joel, 1960s; cuid2227 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Todd, Leonard, undated; cuid2228 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Tongobarch, Vincent, undated; cuid2229 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Tooney, Nancy, 1986; cuid2230 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Topfer, Morton L., 2001; cuid2231 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Torn, Laurence, undated; cuid2232 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Towl, Ted, 1911; cuid2233 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Townsend, Paul B., undated; cuid2234 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Trabold, Andrew Frank, undated; cuid2235 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Tran, Duong, undated; cuid2236 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Trani, John M., 1993; cuid2237 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Trump, John George, 1954; cuid2238 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Truxal, John, 1957; cuid2239 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Tsang, Andy, circa 2005; cuid2240 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Tsao, Robert H. C., circa 1997; cuid2241 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Tsifrinovich, Vladimir, undated; cuid2242 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Tsotras, Vassilis J., undated; cuid2243 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Tucker, Marion, undated; cuid2244 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Tully, John, undated; cuid2245 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Turaun, George A., circa 1954; cuid2246 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Turi, Edith, 1996, circa 2000; cuid2247 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Turiel, David, undated; cuid2248 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Tzes, Anthony P., undated; cuid2249 (Box 8, Folder 131)
- U
  - Ughetta, Henry L., undated; cuid2250 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Ugwa, Okay, undated; cuid2251 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Ujazdowski, T. J., undated; cuid2252 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Ullman, Robert, undated; cuid2253 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Ulman, Abraham, 1999; cuid2254 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Ulman, Hanna A., undated; cuid2255 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Umanskiy, Vladimir, undated; cuid2256 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Ungar, J. Stephen, 1956; cuid2257 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Uzun, Necdet, undated; cuid2258 (Box 8, Folder 140)
- V
  - Vacca, Louis N., undated; cuid2259 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Vafakos, William P., 1978; cuid2260 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Valle, Fabio Della, undated; cuid2261 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Van Cook, Charles F., undated; cuid2262 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Van Horn, John R., undated; cuid2263 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Van Norden, E. M., 1955; cuid2264 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Van Slyke, Richard, undated; cuid2265 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Van Wagenen, Lindsey, undated; cuid2266 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Van Wie, Jonathan, undated; cuid2267 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Van Wynen, Kenneth, undated; cuid2268 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Varmis, undated; cuid2269 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Vathke, Otto W., undated; cuid2270 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Veeraraghavan, Malathi, 2001; cuid2271 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Veit, Robert C., circa 1966; cuid2272 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Velazquez, Nydia, 2000; cuid2273 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Vembenil, Juby, circa 1996; cuid2274 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Vemuri, Murali K., undated; cuid2275 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Venner, Julius, undated; cuid2276 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Vermilye, Rodney J., undated; cuid2277 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Vesce, V.C., undated; cuid2278 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Viets, Herman, circa 1995; cuid2279 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Vignola, Paul, undated; cuid2280 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Villa, S. Santos, undated; cuid2281 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Vincent, Patrick J., undated; cuid2282 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Vineyard, George, circa 1978; cuid2283 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Viola, Frank J., undated; cuid2284 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Voci, Frank, undated; cuid2285 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Vogel, Alice, 1966; cuid2286 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Vogl, Otto, circa 1982, 1994; cuid2287 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Voltz, Peter, 2000; cuid2288 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Von Karmen, Theodore, undated; cuid2289 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - VonPuttkamer, Jesco H., undated; cuid2290 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Vradis, George C., circa 1995; cuid2291 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Vuffson, Evgeny, undated; cuid3621 (Box 8, Folder 173B)
  - Vulanti, Thomas, undated; cuid2292 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Vybiral, undated; cuid2293 (Box 8, Folder 175)
- W
  - Waddell, Russell, circa 1954; cuid2294 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Wagman, Jack, 1938; cuid2295 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Wagner, Robert, circa 1975; cuid2296 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Walker, Burt, undated; cuid2297 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Walker, W.F., circa 1960; cuid2298 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Wallace, Richard, circa 1955; cuid2299 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Wallau, Herman Leon, circa 1954; cuid2300 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Wallach, Steven J., undated; cuid2301 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Wallach, Victor, undated; cuid2302 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Waller, Henry, undated; cuid2303 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Waller (nee Lepow), Sylvia, circa 1999; cuid2304 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Walsh, Charles E., undated; cuid2305 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Walsh, John, undated; cuid2306 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Walsh, undated; cuid2307 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Walter, William T., undated; cuid2308 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Walton, Robert E., undated; cuid2309 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Wandmacher, F. Cornelius, 1956; cuid2310 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Wang, Jiun-Nan (Jim), undated; cuid2311 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Wang, Xiaodong, undated; cuid2312 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Wang, Yao, circa 1997; cuid2313 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Warren, Helen, 1978, 1986; cuid2314 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Wasilchuk, Steven, undated; cuid2315 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Wasserman, Steven, undated; cuid2316 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Waterman, Alan T., circa 1962; cuid2317 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Watson, Lester W., circa 1959; cuid2318 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Weaver, Stanley A., circa 1932; cuid2319 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Weber, Ernst (1901-1966), undated; cuid2320 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Weber, Sonya, undated; cuid2321 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wechsler, Harry C., 1981; cuid2322 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wegrzyn, Stanley W., undated; cuid2323 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Wei, Chih, undated; cuid3612 (Box 9, Folder 5B)
  - Weil, Edward, undated; cuid2324 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Weil, Robert T., Jr., undated; cuid2325 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Weill, George, undated; cuid2326 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Weiman, David N., undated; cuid2327 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Wein, Joel, undated; cuid2328 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Weindling, Ralph E., circa 1998; cuid2329 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Weinman, Eugene A., undated; cuid2330 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Weiner, James R., undated; cuid2331 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Weintraub, Ruth, undated; cuid2332 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Weintraub, Stanley B., undated; cuid2333 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Weiser, Sidney, 1939; cuid2334 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Weiss, Gerald, undated; cuid2335 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Weiss, Marvin D., undated; cuid2336 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Weissberger, A., undated; cuid2337 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Weisstuch, Donald N., 1999, 2002; cuid2338 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Welch, Herbert, 1962; cuid2339 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Wellbrock, Richard, undated; cuid2340 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Wendt, undated; cuid2341 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wendt, Arthur S., undated; cuid2342 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wener, Richard, undated; cuid2343 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wentzel, Lewis A., circa 1937; cuid2344 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Wenzel, Alfred C., undated; cuid2345 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Weseman, Edwin J., circa 1939; cuid2346 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - West, Warren J., circa 1966; cuid2347 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Westermann, David, 1976; cuid2348 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Whalen, Robert J., undated; cuid2349 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Whang, Sung, 1986; cuid2350 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Whang (brothers), circa 1955; cuid2351 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wheeler, Harold A., circa 1996; cuid2352 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Whidden, James T., 1956; cuid2353 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Whipple, Clyde, circa 1955, 1962; cuid2354 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Whipple, Melville C., undated; cuid2355 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - White, George R., undated; cuid2356 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - White, J.L., undated; cuid2357 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - White, William Augustus, photocopies of 1880 photo; cuid2358 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Whitehead, Herbert G., undated; cuid2359 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Whitley, Arthur F., undated; cuid2360 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Whitmore, Carl, circa 1953; cuid2361 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Whitmore, Willet F., undated; cuid2362 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Wich, Emil A., undated; cuid2363 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Widnall, Sheila, undated; cuid2364 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Wieber, George A., undated; cuid2365 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Wiederhorn, Norman, undated; cuid2366 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wiedersum, Frederic G., undated; cuid2367 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wiegand, Dick, 1992; cuid2368 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Wiener, Anthony J., undated; cuid2369 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wigner, Eugene Paul, undated; cuid2370 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wikstrand, William C., undated; cuid2371 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wilcken, Henry J., undated; cuid2372 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wilcox, George L. (1915-2002), 1953; cuid2373 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wildermuth, Gordon, 1976; cuid2374 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Williams, Blair, undated; cuid2375 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Williams, Dennis C., undated; cuid2376 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Williams, Frank H., 1961; cuid2377 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Williams, Robert P., Lieutenant, 1952; cuid2378 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Willig, George H., 1977; cuid2379 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wilson, Robert E., 1940; cuid2380 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Winkert, John W., circa 1951; cuid2381 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Winsche, Warren, 1939; cuid2382 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Winters, Warrinton, undated; cuid2383 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Wishert, John C., Major, 1954; cuid2384 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Wishnick, William, undated; cuid2385 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Witryk, Ted, 1999; cuid2386 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Witt, Christopher J., undated; cuid2387 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Witte, Arnold, undated; cuid2388 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Wojan, Clifford, undated; cuid2389 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Wolf, Barry, 1978; cuid2390 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Wolf, Edward L., undated; cuid2391 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Wolfe, Don M., undated; cuid2392 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Wolfgang, 1954; cuid2393 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Woll, William K., 1966; cuid2394 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Wong, Edward K. "Ted", undated; cuid2395 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Wonsicki, Edward A., Jr., 1959; cuid2396 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Wotherspoon, Neil, undated; cuid2397 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Wovomestko, Frederick, undated; cuid2398 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Wright, Chilton A., undated; cuid2399 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Wuestefeld, [Richard ?], undated; cuid2400 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Wulff, [Raymond ?], undated; cuid2401 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wulfken, Howard J., 1953, 1961; cuid2402 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Wunsch, Joseph W., 1959, 1965; cuid2403 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Wunsch, Elsie and Martin, 1996; cuid2404 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Wunsch, Samuel, 1958, 1967; cuid2405 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Y
  - Yang, Deane, undated; cuid2406 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Yang, Yisong, undated; cuid2407 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Yanis, Edward M., undated; cuid2408 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Yates, Chauncey V., Jr., undated; cuid2409 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Yates, Janet, undated; cuid2410 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Yeoman, Neil, 1955; cuid2411 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Ying, Nelson, 1997; cuid2412 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Yokelson, Bernard J., undated; cuid2413 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Yokelson, Marshall V., undated; cuid2414 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Yoon, Lisa, undated; cuid2415 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Youla, Dante C., undated; cuid2416 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Young, Morris, undated; cuid2417 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Yousoufian, Hrant H., undated; cuid2418 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Yuan, [J.], undated; cuid2419 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Yusim, Galina, undated; cuid2420 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Z
  - Zabar, Zivan, circa 1995; cuid2421 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Zach, Theodore A., 1955; cuid2422 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Zahner, [Richard ?], undated; cuid2423 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Zauderer, Erich, undated; cuid2424 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Zeldin, Martin, undated; cuid2425 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Zerban, Alexander H., undated; cuid2426 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Zhang, GaoYong, undated; cuid2427 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Ziegler, Edward, 1993; cuid2428 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Ziegler, Henry Martin, 1956; cuid2429 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Ziehl, Charles, undated; cuid2430 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Zienkowicz, J.J., 1943; cuid2431 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Ziv, Nina, undated; cuid2432 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Zito, Frederick A., undated; cuid2433 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Zitzmann, Frank Richard, 1956; cuid2434 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Zlatanova, Jordana, undated; cuid2435 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Zucker, Frederic E., circa 1980; cuid2436 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Zuckerman, Robert, undated; cuid2437 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Zurawsky, Walter, undated; cuid2438 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Zworykin, Vladimir K., undated; cuid2439 (Box 9, Folder 121)
- Miscellaneous
  - Unknown- Polytechnic Fellows, undated; cuid2440 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2441 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2442 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Unknown, undated; cuid2443 (Box 9, Folder 125)